closeoption.com 2019-04-16

# Privacy Policy • CloseOption

  * The Company is dedicated to protecting clients' account information and preventing the misuse of documents submitted by clients. But if the legal entity makes the request of the account information in accordance with international law, client's account information will be exchanged with the legal entity.

  * With registration and opening an account, a person guarantees that has understood all the Binary Options and Forex market risks and trading system. So they have opened an account and accept the risk of this market which could erase the partial or total amount of client's money.

  * While using our Services, we may ask you to provide us personal identifiable information that can be used to contact you. Personal identifiable information includes your name, phone number, postal address or other information ("Personal Information").

  * We collect information that your browser sends whenever you visit our Service ("Log Data"). This Log Data may include information such as your computer's Internet Protocol ("IP") address, browser type, browser version, pages you visit plus time and date of your visit, and other statistics.

  * The Company makes all its efforts to update prices and services for clients, but if a problem occurs from Company's side and causes damages to the client, the Company tries to return client's loss. Generally, a Company does not have any obligation to pay the loss of the client.

  * If a client makes a profit in any way such as hacking, software abuse, and his account will be taken over in favor of the Company.

  * The Client must accept and declare that the deposit is not coming from illegal ways in our Company like money laundering, drugs and etc.

  * The client must accept to avoid investing money that cannot keep it and it is better to consult with some experts before entering the financial markets, especially in Binary Options.

  * All information, which has been introduced in our Website, is included the price of currencies, market forecasts, educational materials, social networks and other information. The client is responsible for using this information and materials.

  * It is the client’s responsibility to recognize the company referral which is being introduced by others.

  * Company has the right to ban the client's account unless some points should be clear enough. For example, client does something illegally and maybe the client is obligated to pay the debts such as failure to pay the government taxes, bank debts, personal debts that brings a complaint against the clients.

  * Clients are responsible for their own account security and must not try to log into their accounts from non-personal computers so if something occurs like this, they have to change the password immediately.

  * Due to security reasons, Company account holders or individual clients might be required to send updated identification documents.

  * Once the contract published on the website so clients are responsible for checking it to be aware of all changes happened recently.

  * Cookies are files with small amount of data, which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a web site and stored on your computer's hard drive.

  * We use "cookies" to collect information. You can set your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our Service.

  * We may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate our Service, to provide the Service on our behalf, to perform Service-related services or to assist us in analyzing how our Service is used. These third parties have access to your Personal Information only to perform these tasks on our behalf and are obligated not to disclose or use it for any other purpose.

  * The security of your Personal Information is important for us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially, it means to protect your Personal Information so we cannot absolute guarantee it.

  * Our Service may contain links to other sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third party link, you will be directed to that third party's site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of every site you visit.

  * We have neither control over nor responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third party sites or services.

  * Children under 18 are not allowed to join in our Contest. If we realize it, your account will be removed immediately. Moreover, providing that you are parent and you are aware of your children being with us, please let us know.

  * We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. We will announce all changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page.

  * It is highly recommend that it is better to review the Privacy policy regularly. 

  * If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please [contact us.](https://www.closeoption.com/contact-us)
